The Little family just got bigger.
Stuart Little is a family, fantasy, comedy film directed by Rob Minkoff.
When the Littles adopt Stuart, the mouse, George is initially unwelcoming to his new
brother, and the family cat, Snowbell, is even less enthusiastic.
Stuart resolves to face these difficulties with as
much pluck and courage as he can muster.
Stuart Little (voice), played by Michael J. Fox.
Mrs. Little, played by Geena Davis.
Mr. Little, played by Hugh Laurie.
George Little, played by Jonathan Lipnicki.
Snowbell (voice), played by Nathan Lane.
Smokey (voice), played by Chazz Palminteri.
Stuart Little is a 1999 American live-action
animated comedy film loosely based on E.
White's novel of the same name.
Directed by Rob Minkoff in his live-action
directorial debut, with a screenplay by M.
Night Shyamalan and Greg Brooker, the film features an ensemble cast consisting of Geena
Davis, Hugh Laurie and Jonathan Lipnicki, with the voices of Michael J.
Fox as the titular character, Nathan Lane, Chazz Palminteri,
Steve Zahn, Bruno Kirby and Jennifer Tilly.
It was Estelle Getty's final film role.
Stuart Little premiered in Westwood at Mann Village Theatre on December 5, 1999, and was
released in the United States on December 17, 1999, by Columbia Pictures.
The film received generally positive reviews and became a box
office success, grossing over $300 million worldwide.
It was nominated for an Academy Award for Best
Visual Effects, but lost to The Matrix.
After its success, it also started a franchise with the sequel Stuart Little 2 in 2002, the short-lived television
series Stuart Little in 2003, and the direct-to-video sequel Stuart Little 3: Call of the Wild in 2006.
The film explores themes of sibling relationship, based on
novel or book, cat, gangster, orphanage.
The tone is lighthearted.